const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A second year MBBS student performed experiments related to the sense of taste in the physiology lab. Which of the following taste sensation will have the lowest stimulation threshold?","answers":[{"option":"Acid","bool":false},{"option":"Sweet","bool":false},{"option":"Salty","bool":false},{"option":"Sour","bool":false},{"option":"Bitter","bool":true}]},{"id":1,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which muscle is pierced by the parotid duct?","answers":[{"option":"Buccinator","bool":true},{"option":"Lateral pterygoid","bool":false},{"option":"Zygomaticus major","bool":false},{"option":"Medial pterygoid","bool":false},{"option":"Masseter","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"What is the refractive index of the lens?","answers":[{"option":"1.00","bool":false},{"option":"1.40","bool":true},{"option":"1.38","bool":false},{"option":"1.34","bool":false},{"option":"1.33","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"An 18-year-old man comes to the emergency department with the complaint of inability to completely open his mouth and numbness on his chin and gingiva on his lower jaw after a motorbike accident. On x-ray, diagnosis of fracture of symphysis menti is made. Which nerve is responsible for the numbness?","answers":[{"option":"Auricotemporal","bool":false},{"option":"Lingual","bool":false},{"option":"Superior alveolar","bool":false},{"option":"Buccal","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior alveolar","bool":true}]},{"id":4,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient is brought into the emergency department after sustaining a gunshot wound in the temporal fossa. On examination, there is bleeding from the ear. CT scan reveals a fracture of the bony floor of the temporal fossa. Which clinically important structure lies in the floor of the temporal fossa?","answers":[{"option":"Asterion","bool":false},{"option":"Inion","bool":false},{"option":"Nasion","bool":false},{"option":"Pterion","bool":true},{"option":"Obelion","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A boy complains of loss of sensation from the anterior aspect of the tongue. In which nuclei of the brainstem does the nerve carrying the concerned sensation end?","answers":[{"option":"Nucleus of tractus solitaries","bool":true},{"option":"Superior salivatory nucleus","bool":false},{"option":"Nucleus ambiguous","bool":false},{"option":"Spinal nucleus of trigeminal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Motor nucleus of facial","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"An athlete arrives at the emergency department with a dislocated jaw due to a fall injury while running. He complains of difficulty in swallowing and speaking. Reduction of the mandible is prescribed as a treatment plan. Which muscle initiates the depression of the dislocated bone?","answers":[{"option":"Temporalis","bool":false},{"option":"Medial pterygoid","bool":false},{"option":"Masseter","bool":false},{"option":"Buccinator","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral pterygoid","bool":true}]},{"id":7,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A boxer comes to the emergency department due to a blowout fracture caused by a direct hard blow to his face by his opponent. The x-ray confirms a fracture of the orbital floor. Which nerve is most likely to be damaged due to the blowout?","answers":[{"option":"Supraorbital","bool":false},{"option":"Supratrochlear","bool":false},{"option":"Optic","bool":false},{"option":"Short ciliary","bool":false},{"option":"Infraorbital","bool":true}]},{"id":8,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"The infraorbital fissure is posteriorly between the maxilla and the greater wing of the sphenoid bone. Which fossa communicates with this fissure?","answers":[{"option":"Anterior cranial","bool":false},{"option":"Infratemporal","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior cranial","bool":false},{"option":"Supratemporal","bool":false},{"option":"Pterygopalatine","bool":true}]},{"id":9,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Second-year medical students were asked to expose the muscles of sub-occipital triangle on a cadaver. Which of the following muscles is likely to be found?","answers":[{"option":"Longus capitis","bool":false},{"option":"Rectus capitis posterior","bool":true},{"option":"Scalene medius","bool":false},{"option":"Levator scapulae","bool":false},{"option":"Splenius capitis","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"During rhinoplasty, an ENT surgeon needs to give an incision to the five layers of the external nose. In which of the following layers lie the muscles?","answers":[{"option":"Third","bool":true},{"option":"Forth","bool":false},{"option":"First","bool":false},{"option":"Second","bool":false},{"option":"Fifth","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A 25-year-old male presents to the emergency department with a stab wound in the neck region directed into the submandibular triangle with tongue deviation. Which of the following nerves was damaged?","answers":[{"option":"Glossopharyngeal","bool":false},{"option":"Trigeminal","bool":false},{"option":"Facial","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory","bool":false},{"option":"Hypoglossal","bool":true}]},{"id":12,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"What is the action of the superior oblique muscle on the eyeball?","answers":[{"option":"Adduction, intorsion, and depression","bool":false},{"option":"Adduction, extorsion, and depression","bool":false},{"option":"Abduction, intorsion, and depression","bool":true},{"option":"Abduction, extorsion, and elevation","bool":false},{"option":"Adduction, intorsion, and elevation","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which movement of the eyeball will occur when the superior rectus and inferior oblique contract together?","answers":[{"option":"Elevation","bool":true},{"option":"Abduction","bool":false},{"option":"Adduction","bool":false},{"option":"Intorsion","bool":false},{"option":"Depression","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which movement of the eyeball will occur when the inferior rectus and superior oblique contract together?","answers":[{"option":"Depression","bool":true},{"option":"Adduction","bool":false},{"option":"Elevation","bool":false},{"option":"Abduction","bool":false},{"option":"Intorsion","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"The pterygopalatine fossa communicates with the middle cranial fossa through which of the following passages?","answers":[{"option":"Pterygomaxillary fissure","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenopalatine foramen","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior orbital fissure","bool":false},{"option":"Palatovaginal canal","bool":false},{"option":"Foramen rotundum","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Olfactory epithelium can get damaged by inhalation of toxic fumes and causes physical injury to the nose by the use of nasal spray. What can this lead to?","answers":[{"option":"Insomnia","bool":false},{"option":"Anosmia","bool":true},{"option":"Diplopia","bool":false},{"option":"Anorexia","bool":false},{"option":"Hemianopia","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which nerve supplies the platysma muscle?","answers":[{"option":"Mandibular branch of trigeminal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Branch of glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Branch of accessory spinal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Cervical branch of facial nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Branch of vagus nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which nerve lesion results in contralateral motor loss of the inferior half of the face?","answers":[{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Corticonuclear","bool":true},{"option":"Hypoglossal","bool":false},{"option":"Corticospinal","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A newborn may present with caput succedaneum, leading to prolonged labor. The swelling is present in which layer of the scalp?","answers":[{"option":"Scalp and periosteum","bool":false},{"option":"Aponeurosis and areolar tissue","bool":false},{"option":"Connective tissue and aponeurosis","bool":true},{"option":"Loose areolar tissue and pericranium","bool":false},{"option":"Skin and connective tissue","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which type of salivary gland secretes thin, watery, and rich in enzyme fluid only?","answers":[{"option":"Von Ebners","bool":false},{"option":"Sublingual","bool":false},{"option":"Glands of palate","bool":false},{"option":"Parotid","bool":true},{"option":"Submandibular","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which nerve passes through the root of the neck?","answers":[{"option":"Accessory cranial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Hypoglossal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Vestibulocochlear nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following structures is a prominent feature of the lateral wall of the middle ear cavity?","answers":[{"option":"Canal for the tensor tympani muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Aditus to mastoid antrum","bool":false},{"option":"Pyramidal process","bool":false},{"option":"Epitympanic recess","bool":true},{"option":"Facial canal","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"The medial wall of the pterygopalatine fossa has which of the following opening?","answers":[{"option":"Foramen rotundum","bool":false},{"option":"Pterygomaxillary fissure","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenopalatine foramen","bool":true},{"option":"Pterygoid canal","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior orbital fissure","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Histological features of an organ demonstrated mucosa lined by stratified squamous nonkeratinized epithelium with papillae. The core of the organ is of skeletal muscles. Which of the following organ matches this description?","answers":[{"option":"Pharynx","bool":false},{"option":"Hard palate","bool":false},{"option":"Soft palate","bool":false},{"option":"Palatine tonsils","bool":false},{"option":"Tongue","bool":true}]},{"id":25,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"In a histology practical, some students were asked a question regarding a major salivary gland of pure serous nature. Trauma to that salivary gland causes damage to the nerve resulting in the loss of a section of the muscle of facial expression. Which nerve is involved?","answers":[{"option":"Glossopharyngeal","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus","bool":false},{"option":"Occulomotor","bool":false},{"option":"Facial","bool":true},{"option":"Trochlear","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A histopathologist was observing a slide of a gland under the microscope. It had darkly stained acini with the apical portion of cells filled with secretory granules with striated ducts. Which gland was being observed by the histopathologist?","answers":[{"option":"Sublingual","bool":false},{"option":"Thyroid","bool":false},{"option":"Parotid","bool":true},{"option":"Parathyroid","bool":false},{"option":"Submandibular","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"While observing the microscopic features of the tongue, which of the following papillae is thread-like, deficient in taste buds, and present on the superior surface of the tongue?","answers":[{"option":"Vallate","bool":false},{"option":"Fungiform","bool":false},{"option":"Circumvallate","bool":false},{"option":"Filiform","bool":true},{"option":"Foliate","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Meibomian glands are modified sebaceous glands present on which layer of the eyelid?","answers":[{"option":"Epidermis of skin","bool":false},{"option":"Dermis of skin","bool":false},{"option":"Tarsal plate","bool":true},{"option":"Mucous layer","bool":false},{"option":"Muscular layer","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"The cancer of the submandibular gland has involved a duct lined by low columnar secretory cells having multiple mitochondria at the base. Also, the duct involved is intralobular. Which of the following ducts is involved?","answers":[{"option":"Intercalated duct","bool":false},{"option":"Terminal duct","bool":false},{"option":"Excretory duct","bool":false},{"option":"Interlobular duct","bool":false},{"option":"Striated ducts","bool":true}]},{"id":30,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following layers of the cornea cannot regenerate, leading to corneal scarring?","answers":[{"option":"Endothelium","bool":false},{"option":"Descemets membrane","bool":false},{"option":"Stroma","bool":false},{"option":"Epithelium","bool":false},{"option":"Bowman's membrane","bool":true}]},{"id":31,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient is seen in the neurosurgery clinic with an MRI confirmed pituitary adenoma. Surgical resection of the adenoma is planned. When considering the surgical approach, which paranasal sinus provides access to the pituitary gland?","answers":[{"option":"Frontal sinus","bool":false},{"option":"Anterior ethmoidal air cells","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary sinus","bool":false},{"option":"Middle ethmoidal air cells","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenoid sinus","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient complains of frontal sinus pressure. You determine that it is an infection and administer mucosal shrinking medication. The mucous will then drain into the nasal cavity through which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Nasolacrimal duct","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior nasal meatus","bool":false},{"option":"Spheno-ethmoidal recess","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenopalatine canal","bool":false},{"option":"Semilunar hiatus","bool":true}]},{"id":33,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following veins is not a tributary of the pterygoid venous plexus?","answers":[{"option":"Infraorbital vein","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenopalatine vein","bool":false},{"option":"Greater palatine vein","bool":false},{"option":"Pharyngeal vein","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary vein","bool":true}]},{"id":34,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which pharyngeal arches are the middle ear ossicles derived from?","answers":[{"option":"4th and 6th","bool":false},{"option":"3rd and 6th","bool":false},{"option":"3rd and 4th","bool":false},{"option":"2nd and 3rd","bool":false},{"option":"1st and 2nd","bool":true}]},{"id":35,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Failure of fusion of which of the following causes unilateral oblique cleft lip?","answers":[{"option":"Frontonasal prominence with maxillary prominence","bool":false},{"option":"Two medial nasal prominence","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary prominence with lateral nasal prominence","bool":false},{"option":"Two mandibular prominence","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary prominence with medial nasal prominence","bool":true}]},{"id":36,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which part does the sensory retina develop from?","answers":[{"option":"Pars ciliaris retinae","bool":false},{"option":"Pars optica retinae","bool":true},{"option":"Outer layer of optic cup","bool":false},{"option":"Pars ividica retinae","bool":false},{"option":"Pars ceca retinae","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"What is the visual faculty that allows us to take in information about space in three dimensions (3D)?","answers":[{"option":"Binocular vision","bool":false},{"option":"Stereopsis","bool":true},{"option":"Visual acuity","bool":false},{"option":"Stereognosis","bool":false},{"option":"Field of vision","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A man in his fifties presents with throbbing eye discomfort, a red eye, headache, and blurred vision. The intraocular pressure was at 60 mmHg, and the opthalmologist suspected glaucoma. What level of intraocular pressure would protect the optic nerve and halt eyesight loss?","answers":[{"option":"30 mmHg","bool":false},{"option":"15 mmHg","bool":true},{"option":"10 mmHg","bool":false},{"option":"25 mmHg","bool":false},{"option":"5 mmHg","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A fourth grader complained that he could not see the board from the back of the classroom. His eyes were checked by an opthalmologist after his mother took him to have any refractive issues corrected. What was the ultimate diagnosis, and which lens was given for correction?","answers":[{"option":"Near sightedness and gave spherical lenses for correction","bool":false},{"option":"Hyperopia and gave concave lenses for correction","bool":false},{"option":"Myopia and gave spherical lenses for correction","bool":false},{"option":"Far sightedness and gave spherical lenses for correction","bool":false},{"option":"Near sightedness and gave concave lenses for correction","bool":true}]},{"id":40,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient visits the outpatient department due to ongoing headache symptoms. He claims to be experiencing visual issues, including an inability to see what is coming from the side. This resulted in the suspension of his driving privileges. Based on the information provided, his condition is described as which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Homonymous hemianopia","bool":false},{"option":"Bitemporal hemianopia","bool":true},{"option":"Binasal hemianopia","bool":false},{"option":"Raised intraocular pressure","bool":false},{"option":"Bilateral lesion of optic tract","bool":false}]},{"id":41,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"In a fraction of a second, after rhodopsin has absorbed light energy, it begins to degrade. Which of these is the immediate product?","answers":[{"option":"Metarhodopsin-I","bool":false},{"option":"Bathorhodopsin","bool":true},{"option":"Lumirhodopsin","bool":false},{"option":"Scotopsin","bool":false},{"option":"Metarhodopsin-II","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following cells sends inhibitory signals backward to regulate the lateral spread of visual signals to neighboring cells to help control the degree of contrast in the visual image?","answers":[{"option":"Ganglion cell","bool":false},{"option":"Bipolar cell","bool":false},{"option":"Amacrine cell","bool":false},{"option":"Horizontal cell","bool":false},{"option":"Interplexiform cell","bool":true}]},{"id":43,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which neurotransmitter is released by rods and cones at their synapses with bipolar cells?","answers":[{"option":"GABA","bool":false},{"option":"Glycine","bool":false},{"option":"Acetylcholine","bool":false},{"option":"Glutamate","bool":true},{"option":"Dopamine","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Once presbyopia has set in, each eye maintains a fixed focus at a nearly constant distance which is unique to the individual's eye anatomy. Which of the following lenses would be the best for a person of advanced age to use to ensure clear vision at all distances?","answers":[{"option":"Cylindrical lens","bool":false},{"option":"Bifocal lens","bool":true},{"option":"Spherical lens","bool":false},{"option":"Biconvex lens","bool":false},{"option":"Biconcave lens","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following sensory modalities is conveyed by free nerve endings?","answers":[{"option":"Smell","bool":false},{"option":"Taste","bool":false},{"option":"Temperature","bool":true},{"option":"Vision","bool":false},{"option":"Sound","bool":false}]},{"id":46,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following factors is accountable for the emotions and memories linked to the sense of smell?","answers":[{"option":"Frontal cortex","bool":false},{"option":"Postcentral gyrus","bool":false},{"option":"Olfactory cortex","bool":true},{"option":"Limbus system","bool":false},{"option":"Temporal lobe","bool":false}]},{"id":47,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"In which of the following situations does one get the greatest depth of focus?","answers":[{"option":"Extremely small size of pupil","bool":true},{"option":"Contraction of ciliary muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Large pupil","bool":false},{"option":"Relaxation of ciliary muscle","bool":false},{"option":"In dark environment","bool":false}]},{"id":48,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which protein is responsible for absorbing light in the retina and for vision?","answers":[{"option":"Fibrin","bool":false},{"option":"Keratin","bool":false},{"option":"Collagen","bool":false},{"option":"Melanin","bool":false},{"option":"Rhodopsin","bool":true}]},{"id":49,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which biochemical form of vitamin A is found in the visual cycle?","answers":[{"option":"Retinone","bool":false},{"option":"Retinyl ester","bool":false},{"option":"Retinaldehyde","bool":true},{"option":"Retinoic acid","bool":false},{"option":"Retinol","bool":false}]},{"id":50,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"What disease is caused by the deficiency of vitamin A?","answers":[{"option":"Strabismus","bool":false},{"option":"Amblyopia","bool":false},{"option":"Xeropthalmia","bool":true},{"option":"Pernicious anemia","bool":false},{"option":"Glaucoma","bool":false}]},{"id":51,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A team of doctors needs to know the exact source of intestinal bleeding in a patient. They radiolabeled (and radioactive atoms) a sample of red blood cells taken from a patient. They then reinject the blood to follow the path of blood in the patient. Which of the following technique is used?","answers":[{"option":"X ray","bool":false},{"option":"CT scan","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound scan","bool":false},{"option":"SPECT scan","bool":true},{"option":"MRI scan","bool":false}]},{"id":52,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A professor was comparing nuclear medicine with conventional radiology. Among the following, which is a characteristic feature of nuclear medicine procedure?","answers":[{"option":"Cannot elaborate upon body functions","bool":false},{"option":"Shows structure only","bool":false},{"option":"Beams of radiation pass through the body","bool":false},{"option":"Radioactive material is injected, ingested, or inhaled","bool":true},{"option":"Mainly used in diagnosis","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient intends to seek advice for his forthcoming travel tour to Kenya. He visits the clinic for advice on vaccination, precautions, and chemoprophylaxis. Among the following, which branch of medicine deals specifically with the patient's queries?","answers":[{"option":"Geriatrics","bool":false},{"option":"Emporiatrics","bool":true},{"option":"Infectious diseases","bool":false},{"option":"Epidemiology","bool":false},{"option":"Geriatric medicine","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A 50-year-old man comes to the outpatient department with the feeling as if he was floating or if the world was spinning. The affected nerve responsible for this condition receives motor sensation from which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Cochlea","bool":false},{"option":"Saccule","bool":false},{"option":"Semicircular canal","bool":false},{"option":"Vestibule","bool":true},{"option":"Utricle","bool":false}]},{"id":55,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"A patient comes to the family physician with a complaint of pain in the temporomandibular joint that gets worse during the opening of the mouth. After examination and investigation, diagnosis of forward dislocation of mandible is made. Which factor does not normally oppose the forward movement of this bone?","answers":[{"option":"Masseter","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral pterygoid","bool":true},{"option":"Medial pterygoid","bool":false},{"option":"Temporalis (posterior fibres)","bool":false},{"option":"Articular eminence","bool":false}]},{"id":56,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"The presynaptic parasympathetic fibers to the otic ganglion in the infratemporal fossa are carried by which of the following nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Carotid sinus","bool":false},{"option":"Deep petrosal","bool":false},{"option":"Lesser petrosal","bool":true},{"option":"Auriculotemporal","bool":false},{"option":"Greater petrosal","bool":false}]},{"id":57,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Involuntary fixation is the ability to keep a selected object in your visual field once it has been found via a combination of drifting and flickering movements. Which of the following is most responsible for the loss of this ability?","answers":[{"option":"Superior colliculus","bool":true},{"option":"Inferior colliculus","bool":false},{"option":"Medial longitudinal fasciculus","bool":false},{"option":"Trochlear nerve nucleus","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior colliculus muscle","bool":false}]},{"id":58,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"Which of the following pupillary responses is seen in the Argyll Robertson pupil?","answers":[{"option":"Failure to respond to accommodation but responds to light","bool":false},{"option":"Normal response to light and accommodation","bool":false},{"option":"Failure to respond to accommodation only","bool":false},{"option":"Failure to respond to both accommodation and light","bool":false},{"option":"Failure to respond to light but responds to accommodation","bool":true}]},{"id":59,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2023","question":"How many times as much force is applied to the cochlear fluid as applied to the tympanic membrane by sound waves?","answers":[{"option":"17 folds","bool":false},{"option":"30 folds","bool":false},{"option":"1.3 folds","bool":false},{"option":"22 folds","bool":true},{"option":"55 folds","bool":false}]}]
export default arr